thexyz.info 2016-07-23

# Thexyz Privacy Policy

### Our privacy policy is really simple, we believe your data is your data and you own that data, here you can read more about it including the privacy of your **account** , payment information, registration data and our cookies.

Last updated: March 14th 2013   PRIVACY OF YOUR PAYMENT DETAILS We use encrypted SSL connection to process your credit card information and DO NOT store any of your payment details in our system. The payments are carried out in the background by the PayPal payment processing gateway and go through the HSBC bank’s terminal. Working with the two leaders in online payment operations, we guarantee fast and secure processing of your payment. Not only do we NOT make a record of your credit card details in our system, but also – for maximum online security – we do NOT share this information with any third party. PRIVACY OF YOUR ACCOUNT We consider your registration data and the content of all your messages private and confidential. Our ad-free webmail does not have any tracking built into it. We do not participate in, or co-operate with, any kind of blanket surveillance or monitoring. We also take technical measures where feasible to prevent surveillance of our users occurring without our co-operation, such as:

  * ensuring encrypted access for webmail, IMAP and POP.
  * using [Perfect Forward Secrecy](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Perfect_forward_secrecy) where possible for encrypted connections.
  * using encrypted SMTP for sending your mail when the receiving server supports it.
  * encrypting email while at rest on our servers.
  * encrypting communications between our data centres.

The header of the messages that you send will contain your name (e-mail address) and Internet Protocol (IP) address. We will not monitor or disclose any of your email content or registration data unless we are required to do so: by law, to defend ourselves in any legal action, or to protect our property. Unless prohibited by law, we will disclose to the account holder when we receive a warrant for their account.   Since your password is essential for protecting your privacy, we encourage you to NOT share it with anyone and change it frequently. Additionally, you agree to respect the privacy and confidentiality of others. PRIVACY OF YOUR REGISTRATION DATA Thexyz collects certain information during the registration process. The personally identifiable information that Thexyz collects includes first and last name. Thexyz also collects non-personally identifiable information, such as country, age, gender, etc. You may update your Registration Information at any time from your Web Hosting Control Panel – > My Account – Change Login Credentials section. We may disclose aggregate registration statistics in connection with our marketing activities. WHY WE NEED THIS INFORMATION Your registration information is needed in order for us to operate the site, to provide support for your account, for statistical purposes, etc. Thexyz will NOT send you any unsolicited information, including e-mails, except as mentioned hereby.   New customers will receive a Thexyz welcome e-mail containing information about the features provided by the Service, as well as WHCP (Web Hosting Control Panel) and FTP login details. Thexyz may also send system notifications upon need, related to any upgrade, maintenance or other service issues concerning your hosting account.

Thexyz will keep your personally identifiable information private and will NOT share it with any unauthorized third parties.

COOKIES We use different cookies on our website to make it as useful to you as possible. Cookies are small text files that we put on your computer or mobile device to tell us what you want to use on our site but they do not tell us who you are. [Here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx) you can learn more about cookies and how to [control](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=1) or [delete](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx?page=2) them. Here are the cookies that we use on our site: Essential cookies We use a cookie to remember your login the site login, saving you the trouble of entering your password every time. Also, we set a cookie to help you choose a preferred font size for using the site. These cookies we consider essential for the operation of our website. External web services We use an external live chat service by [ Olark](http://www.olark.com/?r=5mdv01uj) (using cookies to remember your session name) to deliver real time support to you should you want to. While our services are 100% advertisement-free, we do server advertisements within our forums. This helps to ensure our forums are well maintained and kept to decent standard. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

Payment processing To process payments online, we require the billing address for the credit card used and our external payment provider, [Stripe](https://www.stripe.com/)/WorldPay, requires your credit card details. We assume you are happy with this usage of cookies on this website. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or delete the cookies (you can check out how to do that according to your browser [here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)), or browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (named “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari etc.). Please remember that if you choose to delete the cookies or use the browser anonymously, you may find that certain sections of this website do not work properly.
